== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Penny:)I'm really happy
you and Amy are back together.
(Sheldon:)Oh, thank you.
(Leonard:)I'm also really happy, but
I can't pretend it's for you.
New Star Wars in three days!
(Sheldon:)Hey, Thursday can't
get here soon enough.
(Sheldon:)I'm taking off work
to watch the original trilogy
while I eat enough Star Wars
cereal to choke a Wookiee.
(Penny:)Uh, sweetie, you do realize
Thursday is Amy's birthday.
(Sheldon:)And you do realize
I bought my ticket
(Sheldon:)when Amy and I were broken up?
(Sheldon:)I hope you didn't need anything
in that case,
(Sheldon:)'cause it's closed.
(Penny:)You guys just got back together.
(Penny:)You might not want
to ditch her on her birthday.
(Leonard:)I think Penny has a point.
You can see it another day.
(Sheldon:)But someone might
spoil the movie.
(Sheldon:)No one can spoil
Amy's birthday for me.
Surprise! She's even older.
(Sheldon:)Who saw that coming?
Oh, that's nice.
(Penny:)Put that on her cake.
(whirring)